we've grown so much since this started hello agent welcome to the English
……从那以后我们成长了很多……
support
特工你好，欢迎来到Ingress报道
I'm fees on a morir I'm coming to you from Washington DC
我是Susana Moyer，从华盛顿特区发来报道
before like that one of the primary Persepolis anomaly around the globe
这里是Persepolis异常活动的主要场地之一
it supported both the primary and secondary site agents have spent weeks
在全球，为了协助主要及周边异常活动区
planning and coordinating in preparation for what if the be a hard-fought battle
特工们花了数周时间来计划与合作，为将至的一场激烈的战斗做准备
with the united in control it more likely show up the resistant
由于启示军目前控制着更多的Lightman碎片
faith today within even greater challenge the day began in Bratislava
抵抗军面临着更大的挑战
where thousands of agents converged on the historic 50
战斗开始的这一天，上千特工们聚集到了这个有历史的城市Bratislava
agents also gathered with the what they called in pari
在Bari,Cordlia,Thessaloniki,等跨越欧亚非的十个连接区域
Columbia definitely local & Company felt the first
特工们也聚集起来协助他们的队友
Europe Asia and Africa Dr Flex team so we are moving around
我们是个机动队伍
help other rachel's p.m. likely with
因此我们四处转移协助各种行动
go to in barium the political for me it's my first anomaly about so
Bari和Thessaloniki的启示军是最强的
human race second or two
对我来说，这是我的第一次一场活动，而对我们队的其他成员来说，是第二次或第三次了
a free multiple topeka field overby night and supported them
他们在场地上覆盖了多个大field，并以强大的地面行动维护
strong ground I am was a really hot became a
我在此之前曾是个真正的游戏硬核玩家
before that and I am mostly
现在呢
playing press the
我大多数时候玩Ingress
I came from poland
我从波兰那边过来
from or so i'm looking back car ahead hour drive
开了8小时的车过来的
I this the poor Iran 24 hours the now and on the muddy
我现在24小时值守这个Portal
sleep is for the weak if you agree
在异常活动的时候，弱者才睡觉呢
your mission is to get everyone in life am
你同意这么说吧，你们的任务是启示每一个人
my mission is just too annoyed read likely me
而我的任务呢，就是咕噜咕噜，咕噜咕噜~
your honor will be the biggest surprise some also
我们这次最大的惊喜
a re get three books house and
可能就是我们在3秒钟内
the him that bridge that goes this board also
拿下了三个Volatile Portal
from boxer shorts and a bus damer
这些Portal都是8级的还带着AXA盾
summer love such children for improved green
咕噜咕噜咕噜咕噜
2003 those ripple
离开家两千多公里
meeting both printing them
与陌生人见面，去信任他们
didn't compete in and the
而没有咕噜咕噜，咕噜咕噜
than the resistance maintained a firm grip in Cordelia
抵抗军始终牢固的掌握了Cordelia
I'm dominated back to clobber in
并占领了Bratislava
by
咕噜
the power to make it out with the parade of with the resistant turning life in
连接区域的控制被双方瓜分，启示军与抵抗军各控制了5个
each claiming five p.m. nothing controlled Bari
启示军以438比157控制了Bari
438 157 and definitely leaky
486比108控制了Thessaloniki
400 naked pic 108 the resistance it could be a
抵抗军以624比392
with 624 the 392
拿下了Covilha
and Breakfast Club claiming the primary 50 of urban 992
并以4992比1790拿下了主城Brastislava
for 1,790 the first Persepolis anomaly
第一场Persepolis异常活动
belongs to the restricted 6300 making one
胜利由抵抗军以6381比3606取得
the 3600 sick the action then cross the Atlantic
在大西洋的另一头
where agent in America's capital with the time in the day's final outcome
美国首府的特工们将决定这一天的最终结果
they were supported by agency what if there is
来自XXX，Phoenix，Toronto的特工
Phoenix Toronto and connected cells across the Americas
以及全美洲各连接区域的特工们都在协助他们
now we think they can what do you think
好，抵抗军战士们
quiet okay by
今天的胜利会属于你们吗？
free quote today in like a well him a Victorian today
听起来相当自信
kohut motivated by the lost earlier in the day
启示军，今天的胜利会属于你们吗？
the enlightened me to hurt her just getting the CDC like this
或许被今天早先的失败所激励，启示军战士们十分勇猛
really interesting way to get around the city and
就这样，用这样一种真的很有趣的方式来看华盛顿特区，在城市里转悠
visit new places and have a lot of attention 150
造访新的地方，引来很多人的关注，好中二啊
people they initially led across all like
启示军开始时在各个区域都领先
but were overtaken by nations for different effort imported a rich in
但之后被XXX，XXX，Toronto的抵抗军翻盘了
the resistance also led across the connected
抵抗军在6个连接区域领先
felled planing pic to be enlightened 4 make up your own face pic 108
而启示军占有4个
to 580 thick latina your 22
抵抗军以608比586,22分的差距拿下Toronto
and one is a red 303 the 280
303比285拿下Buenos Aires
like a merchant 18 no one leave
胜18分
on the something bigger and i wanna see our pics which fax
我没想看他们搞什么大新闻我就想看到我们阵营赢
stunt part about it is planning a wall tiles and being able to build their
（？？）我们的任务是找到Volatile Portals
first so weird
让他们能够最先抵达
actually helping condition and also being able to walk directly through the
所以我们实际上也是在协助任务
middle
（？？）我们也能够直接走到战场上
competing factions the first
（？？）与敌方阵营交战
I can everything I've been a record high
我什么都做过，我做过记录员
employees I abandoned my everything hard
我做过放脚员，我咕噜咕噜，我什么都做过
character United Nations yards it poppin like
祝贺你！你是终生Zipcar的赢得者
winner how do you feel I feel ecstatic am so excited
感觉怎么样？我高兴疯了，太兴奋了
goodnight now you are they hid was a win at how do you feel
祝贺你！你作为Hint矿泉水赢家，你感觉怎么样？
thank you that's exciting yeah it's missing a hot day like today
谢谢！这太让人兴奋了，啊，特别是在今天这么个大热天
the theme impacted by be in like 10
华盛顿特区的占领方是————
the I
启示军！
in
哦！！！！
you like to maintain feel have a ticket from
启示军在Phoenix始终保持了field
the site 572 184 they also control the primary fight at Washington DC be
以570比184占领了Pheonix
1,432 than 950
他们以1432比956控制了主城华盛顿特区
pic with 3,223
以3273比2651的比分
to keep their perfect 151 the in like health claims the second Persepolis
启示军最终
anomaly
获得了Persepolis活动第二场的胜利
offering BC agents took part in the go
同样是在华盛顿特区，特工们参加了Goruck特别行动挑战
about special ops challenge which revealed but I'll portal
Volatile Portal的信息将发布给完成了活动要求的特工们
to those who completed the demanding course this not just going out and doing
这不仅仅是出去参加个Goruck活动
and doing in Crescent Bank all your actions
或者是玩Ingress
now in effect on your back to be the tip of the spear is absolutely great because
你们的所有行动都会对你们的阵营造成影响
we are the ones trying to find
作为引领者绝对是碉堡了，因为我们是努力找到Volatile Portal的人
the polls are worth the most points and this event so we can win for
在这次活动中这些Portal的分值最高
are fraction in our team and so we are the top dogged
所以为了我们我们的阵营我们的队伍我们能赢，所以我们是夺魁者
right now we're capitalizing on a GRT
目前我们在capitalizing on a GRT experience（？？）
experience to keep are portal
以保证我们的Portal组成部分在一起（？？）
bonaparte together here work together as a team
让大家保持住在一起作为一个队伍行动的状态
but also were using the experience mr. ingress members are senior
我们也在利用我们中的老司机的经验
agents to go ahead and after formals
让他们走在前面抢占Portal
en route whether there alright mission field the yeah this is my first time I
咕噜咕噜有Goruck任务咕噜咕噜
ever gonna go a rockin ever heard the term before I came here
是啊，这是我第一次参加Goruck，我来之前都没听说过这个词
why
ENLIGTENED!
water 1
咕噜
game
这个游戏
really about people of
其实是关于人的，而不是Portal的
older people to hate we've done for let's do this graduate
所有参加Goruck的人们都会说，这个我以前做过，我来教你怎么做
all your like a we've done more like he did very collaborative
你需要说的也是，这个我以前做过，我来教你怎么做，这是一种非常合作性的体验
experience the operation fish agent for their physical and mental image right
这个行动将锻炼特工们到达他们生理和心理的极限
now
目前
we're working to set up and defend our portals testing by leadership and who
我们在建立并防御我们的Portal
work
测试他们的领导力和团队协作能力
you see the two communities merge into one
你看着两个团体融合到一起
doing stuff that you weren't the only goal right vice versa so getaway for two
做一些在Goruck中不会做的事
groups actually go ahead and
这是一个让两组人一起向前，发现一些新东西的好方法
find something new I think it's fun
我觉得很有意思
ingress is a game that gets people out moving walking around and get people
Ingress是个让人们出门转悠的游戏
outdoors
离开家门走走
and they have fun of them
玩起来还充满乐趣
go work gets people outdoors no good gets people move
Goruck也让人们离开家门，是吧，让人们动起来，找些挑战
challenge so they have the same goal
所以他们的目的是一致的
we come up with the two together just like I'm there are no words
我们来把两者结合起来，就好像咕噜咕噜，真的
really I think I will come back to go rock and I think I never
我觉得我会再次参加Goruck的，我觉得我永远不会咕噜咕噜
credit limit one participant agent bit Lake Orion
一个参加活动的特工Bit，之后发了一条G+
keep her pay that he wouldn't trade it for anything with body
说他不会为了任何东西交换咕噜咕噜
anything and own Sunday when the frenetic activity at the anomaly
周日，狂热的异常活动结束后
settled agent that power in a second official mission today
特工们在Brastislava参加了第二个官方任务日
in Bratislava nothing without the history and culture
将自己沉浸于这座古老城市的历史与文化之中
1850 and earning the mission de Barra I'm confident that will make your day
还能拿块任务日的牌子
events in the future
XXX说将来会有更多的任务日
I am also a repeat report but on Friday at he
我还收到一个报告
Intel with 102 agent by a mysterious man in a red baseball cap need of a
在周五，一个带红色棒球帽的神秘男子XXX提交了一份情报
the package was later delivered to me by a bit like the new
包裹之后由特工XXX
across faction greeted by agents he went to great lengths think do it rate per
以及去了XXX保护他的安全通道的跨阵营XXX特工交给了我
I can confirm that the package contains previously
我能确认，这个包裹
on be in shape eclipse apparently intercepted by the issue on surveillance
包含了之前没见过的Shaper符文
program decades ago
明显是被几十年前的ashlang监视计划截获的
what is this mysterious message I will be working to uncover its meaning
这个神秘的信息到底是什么，我将努力揭开它的意义
it with a full day with and turn but when the tough couple
这真是一个辗转周折的充实的一天，而尘埃落定后
the resistant emerged victorious although the enlightened lead
抵抗军是胜利方
420 in terms of controlling the lightning show lifted
尽管启示军在控制Lightman碎片活动中4比0领先
currently controls a perfect little on the theory overall
抵抗军目前依然在总分上控制了Persepolis系列异常活动
90032 8,000 379
9032比8379
following me normally the lightning show at Target Corp for that the 98
异常活动之后，Lightman碎片目标Portal已经反转
with people target now located in kilo picky
抵抗军目标Portal目前位于基隆
and the likely target imprint Monica this pain
而启示军目标则在Santa Monica
open for lunch a killer
这可能对局势有戏剧性的改变
another beginning at the new chapter in the label did he take
或许会成为这个全球范围技巧性争斗活动新篇章的开始
struggled the perfect finale in only four pick played thank you
接下来的一个Persepolis异常活动将在6月20日举行
20th in Hoboken you correct important with her for like 20 per
地点位于 Tohoku, Utrecht and Portland
her Liverpool postman helping they're working
Jakarta, Perth,Liverpool, Poznan, Helsinki ,Milwaukee,Nashville 以及 Ft Collins作为卫星城
masculine for Cali I will be in effect
我将出现在 Utrecht
to cover what is sure to be and its leaking and to mister
见证Persepolis活动的精彩结局
the neck ingress for some today is just a few days away are you
下一个Ingress FS活动将在几天后的6月6日举办
day over the vapors will be taking her really 150 cookies around the world
上千名特工将在全球150多个城市参加这项活动
bring one near you in with dot com class event
你可以在ingress.com/event上找一个你附近的
within the field on the horizon perfect eighth victory
随着我们踏入Persepolis异常活动的最后一周，
strengthened 8 a.m. too hard as we head into the final week the Persepolis
N'zeer初现端倪，XXX的胜利使ADA和Jahan变得更强了
will be here for more than I and respected no
随着Lightman碎片的争抢日益激烈
trapped within the local network as the battle for the Lightning shows
我们将看到更多
intensified
目前困在Portal网络中的Niantic研究人员
they didn't continue to reshape the world he'll
随着特工们不断的改造着世界
sitcom far away from Washington DC
答案也注定不会太遥远了
for the inquest report I'm he's an employer omnivorous
这里是来自华盛顿特区的Ingress报道，我是Susana Moyer
seeking but I will not be found
我是XXX，但是你们找不到我 翻译：skyfalco 校译：AndrewShen 时间轴、压制：SgrAlpha 北京绿军加工出品，感谢观看！